6.x-1.0: First version of Content Glider for Drupal 6
         No conflict with Drupal collapse feature
         Able to set how many content to be glide
6.x-1.1: Fixed: width change to 95% to avoid overlapping in the layout
6.x-1.2: New: Link uses Drupal path rather than node/nid 
         Fixed: Check if DB result empty
6.x-1.3: Fixed: do not display empty teaser
6.x-1.4: Fixed: Block Title use $glider_id and 
         New: Add instruction to README.TXT
         Fixed: show better error message when no content exists
6.x-1.5: Fixed: set background white to transparent, remove width 95% and 100%
         Fixed: disable javascript alert when content not available
         Fixed: hide underline for link